Hello everyone we are the grinning Carl Chan!
We just had our second anniversary concert the other day, didn't we?
Yes, we did!
This time we'd like to have a sushi party to celebrate!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much!
We invited a sushi restaurant to our studio this time!
I'm so glad!
Ta-da!
This is the first time we had a sushi chef come to our studio!
So, please accept the grand prize!
Now, let's go to the seats.
Let's go!
Okay.
I'll set up the camera.
Everybody's in.
Yes, we're in.
Now that we're seated, I'd like to start the sushi party.
Yay!
By the way, Yuka-san likes leaf rice cakes this time, so we had her prepare some leaf rice cakes for us!
Leaf rice cake!
The amount of rice cake is amazing!
Wow!
That's a lot!
Where do you want to eat first?
What?
What do you want?
Are you done?
I'll have a leaf cake.
Leaf cake, please.
Wow!
I can see the adults better.
Amazing.
Right in front of me.
I can eat wasabi. That's amazing.
That's so cool.
Like this.
Wow!
Looks so good!
It's so bright.
Wow.
They're all here.
We're all here.
I'm so nervous.
Thank you very much.
Ta-da!
They're here.
Can you see it?
It's shining.
It's great.
Shall we eat then?
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit.
You eat with your hands?
I've never done it before.
How many hands do you eat with?
How do I eat with my hands?
Normal.
Maybe there's a normal way to hold it.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Delicious.
If they eat it, they eat it, right?
I'm so new to YouTube, everyone ate it.
What do you think?
I've never eaten such a fatty leaf cake in my life.
I'm crazy about it.
It's thick.
It's so thick.
Moist.
Let's go, go, go!
How much, please?
Oh, my God.
You're glowing.
Thank you so much.
That's great.
It's so shiny.
It's so shiny, you can almost see our faces in the reflection.
If you look closely.
If you close it up...
It's nice.
I think we're in the reflection.
Can you turn it this way, please?
Yes, sir.
It looks good.
I'm happy.
How do you want it?
Good luck.
Don't look at me for a second.
Up?
It looks like it's about to fall off.
Bon appétit.
How much do you want?
Do you want to munch?
That's nice.
Big fatty tuna.
Looks delicious!
You, too.
Thank you.
I had it with me.
Shall I put it over here?
Thank you very much.
I'd love to see Ayab at the table.
Really?
It's embarrassing to be seen eating.
O-toro.
Bon appétit!
Cut it the way you eat it.
Let's all talk lightly.
Let's talk about our second anniversary.
We did it so fast, didn't we?
But Setori had us do a lot of covers for the first time this time,
It was very fast-paced.
Before I knew it, it was over.
The second anniversary was also very fast-paced,
Was there a lot to learn?
There were many units this time,
I didn't know what everyone was doing.
I pretended I didn't know a lot.
I don't know what I'm not doing. I don't know what they are doing.
It's like learning what they're doing.
That was fun, too. I also enjoyed watching everyone's performances.
It was like a cultural festival performance,
It was like a gathering.
The concept was also fun because the school was there.
I thought that was the hardest part.
The suite trip.
That was difficult.
I can't open it! I thought, "It won't open.
I remember I struggled a lot.
We were all talking about it like hand gestures on TikTok.
We worked hard.
Did you guys hold back on food or anything for the 2nd anniversary?
Not really.
Not at all.
I didn't either.
I ate relentlessly.
On the day of the event, the costume change was the busiest ever,
Fast costume changes.
I couldn't believe how fast some of the girls changed,
Some of them changed their clothes in the middle of a 50-second song,
I thought, "Oh my God.
After changing, we went out on stage right away.
Usually, there is a time to take a breath in the sleeve, but not this time,
But there was none this time.
It was decided that we were going to do it this time.
The flounder is too delicious, everyone.
Is it bad?
If you eat Hirame.
I think I'll have some Hirame.
Can I have some?
It's so delicious.
I'll have some Hirame, too.
Hirame is a white fish?
White fish.
Salmon is a white fish too.
Right?
I guess so.
Yes, it is.
Salmon is a white fish?
That's good.
It's not white.
The food you eat is red.
There is no confirmation.
Oh no.
So cute.
I think the biggest thing for the 2nd anniversary was that Aoi came back to the stage,
I was so happy during the rehearsal when we were practicing for the performance that I was about to cry,
But when I got up on stage for the performance, I was so happy that I almost cried,
I was so happy and almost cried when I was practicing for the performance during rehearsals,
I thought "Near Joy" was really good.
It was amazing.
I thought, "This is a quieter version of this performance,
The performance was great, and Aoi's voice was wonderful,
The production was great, and Aoi's singing voice was wonderful,
I really felt like crying.
You know Aho-san came back to us during the rehearsal?
I screamed.
I was so happy to hear Aho-san, it was so bad.
But personally, I got to see Aho-san dancing without prevention,
I think it was the first time for everyone to see it,
I thought that must have made them very happy.
I thought it must have made everyone happy because it was their first time seeing Aho-san dance.
The opening costume was a new costume that was made for me,
I love all the costumes I have worn so far,
I love all the previous costumes, but this costume made me feel more like an idol.
It's true.
I'm going for the most frilly type among Joy's costumes,
I thought I was an idol.
I was an idol,
You were an idol.
So, what do you want to say?
I thought they were kind of idols,
When I played the role, everyone was sparkling,
They were so cute.
Even looking at Kameko's picture,
I saw Kameko's picture, and her outfit was so sparkly,
They reflected the glitter,
They all look like princesses.
And the toupee.
It has a toupee in it,
Ayumi and I are together,
We have the same hair ornament.
Ayumi had a half-twin this time,
Momoko had a high twin.
I was happy to see the same hair ornament.
Our costumes were different, weren't they?
The length of the skirt was different.
I think Momoko's was shorter.
I heard that the bottom part of the skirt is supposed to be aligned when they stand side by side.
In the group photo,
The one on the side is in a straight line.
It's really beautiful.
Osaru-san came up with the idea to make that line.
It was very detailed.
I really enjoy the rehearsal period.
Thank you very much.
It was so much fun.
There were a lot of cover songs.
I don't have any similarity with Ayumi.
I don't have any similarities with Ayumi, either.
Yuto?
Me, Yuto and Mai wore off-the-shoulder knitwear.
And Omawase Furiko?
The omawase pendulum is Momoko and me.
That's right.
But Ayumi's "beauty under the moon" really made me want to cry.
I almost cried.
When she sang "Remise".
The song was soaked.
It's crystal clear.
Super nice.
It's so beautiful.
I almost cried. Everyone's singing.
Aoi's voice too.
Are their voices getting louder?
It's like they're spinning.
I can tell. I get it.
I could really get into the story of the song "Tsukihitobi".
Everyone was amazing.
Everyone? Really?
It was great.
I was so impressed with the two of them,
Their level of performance was amazing,
It made me want to do my best.
I love those three. I do.
Really? I'm glad.
I'm always sending them things that I do with them,
I've been spending a lot of time with the three of them.
I think it's great.
You were really one of the gorgeous ones.
There were so many cover songs this time.
DJ ALICE.
Even if you call him DJ ALICE, if you call him DJ ALICE, it's still a mystery,
I think it would be something.
DJ ALICE is a DJ,
DJ ALICE DJs and covers various songs for this year's anniversary blog,
I covered a lot of songs by idols that I respect,
It was a lot of fun.
Everyone was nonstop as we connected with each other.
Around September, we had a karaoke contest at the Inoi Joy Thanksgiving Festival,
We had a kind of karaoke contest at the Inoi Joy Grand Thanksgiving Festival in September, right?
There were a lot of songs that we covered at that time,
It was like we were taking a back seat.
We were like, "Oh my God!
It was a surprise, wasn't it?
I was really surprised.
Alice was right,
What? Oh, no.
She was cute. She was really cute.
You were doing your best, Alice.
Alice, you worked really hard.
The costumes and everything, but the props?
Like the mic stand for Konoa's Peach Color One-Sided Love,
It was sparkling and so on,
Ayumi and I did it, and it was my cutest part,
And Fruit Zipper's music,
The production team made it for us,
I was so happy.
I was taking it home with me.
What? Really?
Then please do a food report on hamachi.
Sure.
Yuka, a tasty food report.
Why do you have to have a steering wheel like that?
You can do anything.
Really?
Bon appétit.
You ate it like it was delicious.
Yes, it was.
It's like, "Mmmm...
He ate it.
It's cute.
The fat.
It's delicious.
When you take a bite, a tremendous amount of fresh fat goes right through your body and down your throat,
I am happy.
Happiness has begun.
It was a wonderful food report.
But I did it while I was eating this sushi.
It was manual, wasn't it? The stage set.
A lot of people in the back.
They're talking differently.
Okay, let's talk about the stage set now.
The stage set is amazing, isn't it?
It's manual.
It's amazing that it's done manually.
That's right. Gentlemen. Did you know that?
I mean, so many different people,
Hundreds?
Hundreds of people?
I've been touched by about a hundred people,
At the talk sessions and so on,
They say, "You were so brilliant,
They tell us that they had a great time,
But that's not just because of our efforts,
It's not just us, but many people have supported us,
The costumes, the make-up artists, and the makeup artists,
The costumes, the make-up artists,
the lighting, and so on,
The staff supported us,
I dare to say that the 2nd anniversary was a success, a great success.
That's right. I'm so grateful.
I'm so grateful.
It was magical. When we were on stage.
When I'm on stage.
It's like I'm allowed to be an idol.
And the fans, too.
They were so happy to see us,
I was really happy.
I could see. I could see.
I was able to go to the side of the audience seats and to the standing platform,
I was very close to the audience,
Also, I was able to take a lot of pictures of Kameko-san,
I was very close to the stand,
I searched for pictures of Kameko by Mr. Kameko,
I searched for pictures of Kameko and found that she took pictures of me at a very close distance,
I searched for Kameko's photos of Kameko and found that they were taken at a very close range, and they were so beautiful,
It was really this close, wasn't it?
It was this close, wasn't it?
It was close.
And there were so many people,
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Cary.
Thank you very much. Cary.
You've decided to release your first single.
It's decided.
It's in June. Everyone.
June.
I wonder how it will be.
We're all still excited about it.
We don't know anything yet.
We just want you to really enjoy it.
We want to do our best so that we can create works of art.
A lot of people have picked up the mini-album,
Thank you so much.
I'd like to do my best for the single as well.
I will do my best.
Now that the 2nd anniversary concert is over,
We had a sushi party with everyone.
We had a variety of ingredients, and it was really delicious,
It was a great time for us to look back on the memories of the 2nd anniversary concert,
It was a great time.
What was the best sushi?
It's hard to choose,
I think it was a little bit.
What was your favorite?
The Ootoro was my personal favorite.
It was delicious.
Everything was good, but the otoro.
It was the first time for me to try Hirame at a sushi restaurant,
It was so delicious that I decided to order Hirame when I go to sushi restaurants from now on.
That's good.
So, it was a very enjoyable time, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
That's all for now.
Bye bye.